export default [{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which of the following is oldest Hindu Epic ?",
    "correct_answer": "Ramayana",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Mahabharata", "Ramayana", "Panchtantra", "Ashtadhyayi"],
    "description":""
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which of the following award is highest Civilian Award of India ?",
    "correct_answer": "Bharat Ratna",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Bharat Ratna", "Nobel Prize", "Param veer chakra","Padma Bhushan"],
    "description":""
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "who was the first nobel prize winner in india",
    "correct_answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
    "incorrect_answers": ["C. V. Raman", "Rabindranath Tagore", "Amartya Sen","None of These"],
    "description":""
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which is the Second Smallest continent?",
    "correct_answer": "Europe",
    "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Antarctica", "Europe","Australia"],
    "description":"Europe covers about 10 M square kilometres  or 2% of the Earth's surface (6.8% of land area)"
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the Name of Scientist, who stated that matter can be converted into energy",
    "correct_answer": "Einstein",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Boyle", "Einstein", "Avogadro","Lavoisier"],
    "description":" e = mc2"

}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of the following mountain ranges form the longest mountain chain in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "The Andes of South America",
    "incorrect_answers": ["The Rockies of North America", "The Andes of South America", "Himalayas","Great Dividing Range, Austratila"],
    "description":""
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which state was Ram Nath Kovind serving as governor, just prior to his election as president of India ?",
    "correct_answer": "Bihar",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Uttar Pradesh", "Rajasthan", "Jharkhand","Bihar"],
    "description":""
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": " Who among the youngest Indian woman to win an Olympic medal ?",
    "correct_answer": "P V Sindhu",
    "incorrect_answers": ["P V Sindhu","Hima Das", "Dipa Karmakar", "Saina Nehwal"],
    "description":"She Won silver medal in the women's singles event of the 2016 Summer Olympics, she is the first Indian shuttler to reach the final of an Olympics badminton event."
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which city is recorded as the most polluted megacity in the World by World Health Organisation",
    "correct_answer": "Delhi",
    "description":"Breathing In Delhi Equivalent To Smoking 7 Cigarettes Everyday https://www.makaan.com/iq/latest-real-estate-news/household-air-pollution-the-biggest-contributor-to-premature-deaths-in-india-says-report",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Beijing", "Russia", "China","Delhi"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In India, the Monther's Day is celebrated on _____ Sunday of May month",
    "correct_answer": "2nd",
    "description":" It is celebrated on various days in many parts of the world - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mother%27s_Day",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1st", "2nd", "3rd","4th"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "According to a Hindi proverb, how does a dudh ka jala drink his chanch?",
    "correct_answer": "Phook phook kar",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Nitar nitar kar", "Soongh soongh kar", "Phook phook kar", "Ithla ithla kar"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In 2014,the European union imposed a temporary ban on the import of which of these fruits from India?",
    "correct_answer": "Mangos",
    "description":" Shipments of mangoes from India including the premium Alphonso mangoes, had been stopped after inspections found some consignments infested with fruit flies.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Mango", "Banana", "Mango", "Pineapple"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these battles didn’t involve the Mughal army?",
    "correct_answer": "Third battle of Panipath",
    "description":"The Third Battle of Panipat took place on 14 January 1761 at Panipat, between Maratha Empire and invading forces of the King of Afghanistan, Ahmad Shah Abdali, afgaan won",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "Battle of Buxar", "Battle of Haldighati", "Second battle of Panipath", "Third battle of Panipath"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Before 2014, when was the last time in India that a single party majority was formed at the centre?",
    "correct_answer": "1984",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "1984", "1991","1990","1999"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The potato is believed to have been originated in which of these places?",
    "correct_answer": "South America",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "South America","Asia", "Europe", "Africa"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the main ingredient of Kulcha in Matar Kulcha or Chole Kulcha?",
    "correct_answer": "Maida",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "Daal", "Maida", "Besan", "Suji"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these is shorter than 1 inch?",
    "correct_answer": "2 cm",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "2 cm", "3 cm ", "4 cm","5 cm"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these asuras had a boon that only a son of Shiva could kill him?",
    "correct_answer": "Tarakasura",
    "description":"Tarakasura was a Daitya and the son of Vajranaga (son of Diti and Kashyapa). He was killed by Kartikeya. He had a boon that he could only be killed by a son of Shiva. The purpose of his life was to defeat Indra and the devas.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Mahabali", "Sunda", "Bhasmasura", "Tarakasura"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Complete this Hindi saying, “Duwidha me dono gaye......, mili na Rama”, which means that a confused person loses everything??",
    "correct_answer": "Maya",
    "description":"Duwidha me dono gaye Maya, mili na Rama",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hema", "Maya", "Jaya", "Sushma"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The Gaza strip is bordered by which two countries?",
    "correct_answer": "Israel and Egypt",
    "description":"The Gaza Strip, or simply Gaza, is a self-governing Palestinian territory, that borders Egypt on the southwest and Israel on the east and north. Gaza and the West Bank are claimed by the State of Palestine.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Israel and Egypt", "Israel and Jordan", "Israel and Syria", "Israel and Saudi Arabia"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these words is also a part of the name of an Union Territory of India?",
    "correct_answer": "Haveli",
    "description":"Dadra and Nagar Haveli is a union territory in Western India. It is composed of two separate geographical entities: Nagar Haveli and Dadra. Silvassa is the capital of Dadra and Nagar Haveli.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Chaupal", "Mahal", "Chabutara", "Haveli"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The first Nobel prize in physics was awarded for the discovery of what?",
    "correct_answer": "X ray",
    "description":"The first Nobel Prize in Physics was awarded in 1901 to Wilhelm Conrad Röntgen, of Germany, in December 2007",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Laser", "Transistor", "X ray", "Vacuum tubes"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which month in the Indian calender features an extra day on a leap year?",
    "correct_answer": "Chaitra",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Chaitra", "Jaishthya", "Baishakh", "Phulgun"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What was the capital of Madhya Pradesh before Bhopal?",
    "correct_answer": "Nagpur",
    "description":"After the independence of India, Madhya Pradesh was created in 1950 with Nagpur as the capital of the state. Bhopal Chosen as capital of Madhya Pradesh in 1956.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Indore", "Nagpur", "Jhansi", "Raipur"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these rivers flows through India and another country??",
    "correct_answer": "Ravi",
    "description":"The Ravi River, a transboundary river of India and Pakistan. The waters of the Ravi River drain into the Arabian Sea (Indian Ocean) through the Indus River in Pakistan.",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Yamuna", "Narmada", "Sabarmati", "Ravi"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Who is the only Indian prime minister whose signature is found on a 50 rupee currency notes?",
    "correct_answer": "Manmohan Singh",
    "description":"In 1982, he was appointed Governor of the Reserve Bank of India under then Finance Minister Pranab Mukherjee and held the post until 1985",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Indira Gandhi", "Morarji Desai", "Manmohan Singh", "Inder Kumar Gujral"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these would you find written on cigarette packets sold in India?",
    "correct_answer": "Smoking kills",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Smoking thrills", "Smoking drills", "Smoking chills", "Smoking kills"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In which sporting event did India win the most number of gold medals in the 2014 Commonwealth games??",
    "correct_answer": "Wrestling",
    "description":"Wrestling, total 13 medal, 5 gold,	6 silver, 2 Bronze",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Shooting", "Weightlifting", "Wrestling", "Boxing"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these creatures mainly lays eggs though some of its species also gives birth to young ones??",
    "correct_answer": "Lizards",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Lizards",  "Bats", "Kangaroos", "Rats"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which part of the eye is stored in eye banks for transplant?",
    "correct_answer": "Cornea",
    "description":"The cornea is the transparent front part of the eye that covers the iris, pupil, and anterior chamber. The cornea, with the anterior chamber and lens, accounting for approximately two-thirds of the eye's total optical power.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Cornea", "Iris", "Pupil", "Retina"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The first woman president of India, Pratibha Patil, was the first woman governor of which state ?",
    "correct_answer": "Rajasthan",
    "description":"On 8 November 2004 she was appointed as the 24th Governor of Rajasthan,[7] the first woman to hold that office[8] and according to the BBC was a low-profile incumbent",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Maharashtra","Gujarat", "Goa","Rajasthan"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What does the ‘com’ indicate in ‘.com’ that appears in an Internet Domain Name?",
    "correct_answer": "Commercial",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Commercial", "Computer", "Communication", "Community"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which planet has the shortest year and the longest day in the solar system?",
    "correct_answer": "Mercury",
    "description":"1 Mercury day = 58 earth days, 1 Mercury year  = 88 earth days",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Jupiter","Mercury", "Neptune"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "At what temperature do the Fahrenheit and Celsius scales show the same reading ?",
    "correct_answer": "-40 degrees",
    "description":"°F = (°C * 9/5) + 32",
    "incorrect_answers": ["-60 degrees", "40 degrees","80 degrees","-40 degrees"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In 1610, who first observed the planet Saturn through a telescope?",
    "correct_answer": "Galileo Galilei",
    "description":"Galileo Galilei was the first to observe Saturn and Because of the crudeness of his telescope, He incorrectly guessed that there were two large moons on either side of Saturn.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Galileo Galilei","Nicolaus Copernicus", "Giovanni Cassini", "Giordano Bruno"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "According to a TV ad, Which duo goes to the tailor and says , “Masterji, pitaji ki patloon ek bilang chhoti kar do” ?",
    "correct_answer": "Ramesh – Suresh",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hari – Harish","Santa – Banta", "Ramesh – Suresh", "Ajay – Vijay"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "From which plant, similar to a cactus, is tequila made?",
    "correct_answer": "Blue Agave ",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Blackberries","Blue Agave", "Barley", "oak"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The theory of Evolution which states 'Evolution by natural selection' was produced by",
    "correct_answer": "Darwin ",
    "description":" Charles Darwin formulated the scientific theory of evolution by natural selection, published in his book On the Origin of Species (1859)",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Darwin", "Einstein", "Newton","Mendel"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In which of these regions would you find towns named Pauri and Tehri?",
    "correct_answer": "Garhwal ",
    "description":"Garhwal is the western region of the northern Indian state of Uttarakhand which is home to the Garhwali people.",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Kumaon","Garhwal","Kangra","Mandi"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these festivals is celebrated to commemorate Lord Krishna’s lifting of a mountain?",
    "correct_answer": "Govardhan Puja",
    "description":"Govardhan puja which is also known as Annakoot is celebrated as on this day Lord Krishna had defeated Indra by lifting the Govardhan hill on his little finger. It is usually clelebrated on the fourth day of Diwali.",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Dhanteras","Govardhan Puja","Gokul Ashtami","Gangaur"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these games does not  have a stringed racket?",
    "correct_answer": "Table Tennis",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Lawn Tennis", "Badminton", "Table Tennis","Squash"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Ram Prasad Bismil, Thakur Roshan Singh, Rajendra Nath Lahiri and Ashfaqullah Khan, were all hanged for their role in which of the following??",
    "correct_answer": "Kakori Conspiracy",
    "description":"The Kakori Conspiracy was a train robbery that took place between Kakori and Lucknow, on 9 August 1925. Since the organisation needed money for purchase of weaponry, Bismil and his party decided to plunder a train on one of the Northern Railway lines.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Delhi Assembly bombing","Kakori Conspiracy","Saunders’ Murder","Chori-Chori incident"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": " Which is the largest state in south India in terms of area?",
    "correct_answer": "Karnataka",
    "description":" The state covers an area of 191,976 square kilometres which is 5.83 percent of the total geographical area of India, also the seventh largest Indian state by area.",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Telangana","Karnataka","Tamil Nadu","Andhra Pradesh"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Apart from Bihar’s capital Patna, the name of which state’s capital starts with the letter ‘P’?",
    "correct_answer": "Goa",
    "description":"panjim",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Assam","Goa","Manipur","Telangana"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Arrange these structures in the increasing order of their height. ",
    "correct_answer": "D->B->C->A",
    "description":"Char Minar- 56m, Qutub Minar -73 m, Eiffel Tower- 324m, Burj Khalifa -830m",
    "incorrect_answers": ["(a). Burj Khalifa (Dubai)","(b). Qutub Minar (Delhi)","(c). Eiffel Tower (Paris)","(d). Char Minar (Hyderabad)"]
}, {
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The Statue of Liberty, offically known as 'Liberty Enlightening the World' gifted to the United States of America by which country?",
    "correct_answer": "France",
    "description":"The Statue of Liberty was a gift of friendship from the people of France to the people of the United States  to commemorate the perseverance of freedom and democracy in the United States and to honor the work of the late president Abraham Lincoln",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "England", "Germany","France"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": " If you are doing ‘guzaarish’, then what exactly are you doing ?",
    "correct_answer": "Nivedan",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Tu Tu Main Main","Nivedan", "Nakal", "Mazaak"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Arrange these states and UTs in increasing order of the numbers indicated in their names?",
    "correct_answer": "Tripura -> Punjab -> Chhattisgarh- > Lakshwadeep",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Chhattisgarh", "Tripura", "Punjab", "Lakshwadeep"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "what was the name of Aamir Khan’s character in the Oscar-nominated film 'Lagaan.'",
    "correct_answer": "Bhuvan",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Sajjan", "Arjan", "Bhuvan", "Lallan"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which Amrish Puri film features the iconic dialogue 'Mogambo khush hua'?",
    "correct_answer": "Mr. India",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Nayak: The Real Hero", "Mr. India", "Damini", "Diljale"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which Amrish Puri film features the iconic dialogue 'Mogambo khush hua'?",
    "correct_answer": "Mr. India",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Nayak: The Real Hero", "Mr. India", "Damini", "Diljale"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "From where does Veeru propose to Basanti in Sholay?",
    "correct_answer": "Top of a water tank",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Top of a roof", "Top of a ladder ", "Top of a hill ", "Top of a water tank"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of the following words is a palindrome?",
    "correct_answer": "racecar",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["yacht", "airplane", "racecar", "train"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "With reference to a wedding, What does “Laal Joda” means ?",
    "correct_answer": "Set of Clothes",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "Pair of bangles","Set of Clothes", "Newly Married couple","Milan of Samdhis"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The name of which of these character features in an anti eve-teasing squad formed in the state of Uttar Pradesh ?",
    "correct_answer": "Romeo",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Macbeth","Hamlet", "Othello", "Romeo" ]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these Indian cities is closest to the Pakistani city of Lahore ?",
    "correct_answer": "Amritsar",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "Srinagar","Jaisalmer","Amritsar", "Udhampur"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these gods is also known as Ramapati, Ramakant and Ramaraman ?",
    "correct_answer": "Vishnu",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "Ganesha", "Vishnu","Brahma","Shiva"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these musical instrument is held in one hand and played with the other ?",
    "correct_answer": "Dafli",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Tabla","Santoor","Mridangam", "Dafli"]
},
{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these musical instrument is held in one hand and played with the other ?",
    "correct_answer": "Dafli",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Tabla","Santoor","Mridangam", "Dafli"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In ODI Cricket, who created the record of scoring the fastest century in just 31 balls ?",
    "correct_answer": "AB De Villiers",
    "description":"Villiers broke both the fastest half-ton and century records in the same match , reaching his 50 in just 16 balls, and  century in just 31 balls, vs West Indies, 2015. ",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Corey Anderson","AB De Villiers","Shahid Afridi","Mark Boucher"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The slogan ‘One Nation’, ‘One Tax’, ‘One Market’ was used for the promotion of which tax scheme by the central govt?",
    "correct_answer": "GST",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["GST","DDT","STT", "CST"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What exactly are the ancient pyramids of Giza ?",
    "correct_answer": "Tombs",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Granaries","Lighthouses","Tombs","Palaces"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What exactly are the ancient pyramids of Giza ?",
    "correct_answer": "Tombs",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Granaries","Lighthouses","Tombs","Palaces"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "if we mix all the seven colors of the rainbow, what would the resultant color be?",
    "correct_answer": "White",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["White","Black","Maroon","Dark Blue"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Arrange these sporting events, from the shortest to longest, In terms of the standard duration of each event.",
    "correct_answer": "B->A->C->D",
    "description":"100 m race avg 7-10 sec, Hockey Match 60 minutes, Football Match 90 mins,Test Cricket Match 5 days ",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hockey Match",  "100 m race", "Football Match","Test Cricket Match"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "According to Hindu Mythology, Narada is depicted carrying which musical instrument?",
    "correct_answer": "Veena",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Ektara","Veena","Sitar","Flute"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of the following states does not border Myanmar ?",
    "correct_answer": "Meghalaya",
    "description":"",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Manipur","Meghalaya", "Mizoram", "Nagaland"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Starting with the earliest, arrange these festivals in the order of their celebration in the calendar year of 2018?",
    "correct_answer": "B->D->C->A",
    "description":"makar Sankranti- 14 January, Baisakhi- 14 April, Janmashtami- 2 September, Dussehra- 19 October",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Dussehra","makar Sankranti", "Janmashtami","Baisakhi"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Starting with the earliest, arrange these festivals in the order of their celebration in the calendar year of 2018?",
    "correct_answer": "B->D->C->A",
    "description":"makar Sankranti- 14 January, Baisakhi- 14 April, Janmashtami- 2 September, Dussehra- 19 October",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Dussehra","makar Sankranti", "Janmashtami","Baisakhi"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "How many states in India have a coastline along the Bay of Bengal?",
    "correct_answer": "4",
    "description":"West Bengal, Odisha, AP, Taminadu",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "2", "3", "4","5"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which one of these is not a 21st century invention??",
    "correct_answer": "Google",
    "description":"iPhone released on 2007, Google was founded in 1998, Skype was founded in 2003, youtube was launched on 2005  ",
    "incorrect_answers": ["iPhone","Google","Skype","YouTube"]
},{
    "category": "History",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Which of these is equal to one-third of a yard?",
    "correct_answer": "1 Foot",
    "description":" 1 yard = 3 foot",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1 Foot","24 Inches"," 3 metres", "12 centimetres"]
}]